Now, we have we have executed an impacted command on the column machines and we have the
system 32 directory, you can find that let us shift our table page, you do not want much
privilege here, but it will be running in a system level.
Let us use this terminal to archive our files, what we have discussed, so our file is this
one, rendial32.exe.dom, so this is the file we are going to create archive, so without
GUI or interaction, right?
So my term machine, already have a wind rare, because most of the mission will be most
of the organization machine that was configured with the wind rare, so not a problem, your aim
is to use the wind rare and you can you need to do some kind of collection stuff, okay?
So usually the, usually the wind rare directory was present on the program files folder,
you can you can you can you can you can see here, there is a wind rare.exe was present
on the machine, so let me do one thing, I can use a wind rare.exe a for archive and I'm
going to save my file in the user /public folder /x build dump, okay?
the file, I'm going to collect using the winter, basically I am archiving the file using
the winter, so this is a small example, but the detectors will collect multiple files, I was
collecting a small file okay, I'll move to areas of file users /users/documents/rendll32.exe.db
I hope this is the file, so let's execute this, now the command get execute and you can
see the nothing happened in the machine, so let's move towards the TD public folder, okay?
Yes, it is /users/publictr, so exit, exit, exit, edit, edit, edit, edit this one more
time, but it's said, it's get X field, I have saved an X field in P.x build dump.ra, but I'm
not finding in the public directory, so not a problem, we'll do one more, we'll check one
more time, we flash program file dash here, dash here, let's have the same directory dump.ra
and let's have the files here users/user/documents-rendll32.exe.db, let's see now, let's
find out whether it was created or not, yeah, now the file has created, it was in 0 bytes,
let's do one more time, the AR, yeah, now we are good, here you can find X file, or X
field dump.ra, let's copy this file to our target directory, X field dump.ra to public folder,
so file copied, now let's find out file, was present on the directory, so yeah, now you
can find a file X field.ra that was created now, 736, oh, even my Windows machine time can
be the same, 737 now, so we can find the time here, I'll just create it now, so the time
was showing this, okay, so let's go and check the public folder, so here you can find
the X file dump, that file was present on the machine, so let's check the logs and up
so what actually happened, okay, so we know already we performed something in the, performed
a lot of things in the impacted section, so now it was, it was same, some service has been
created, WRT, something, right, so let's verify that one, yeah, W or something, something
that was created, because I was using the PSXX for in packet, it will not store all the
commands in the system, EVT X, even logs, so only the SMVX will be storing all the logs,
okay, so I hope this will be, this will be one of the best thing we can do while collecting
the data without GUI, user interactions or GUI activity, right, so we can do everything
in the terminal, so you don't need to have any sort of GUI to interact and collect the data,
right, so let's hop off from here and we'll continue our discussion in the next video, see
you guys bye bye.